Arroyos.
Brooks, please stop.
Brooks, who let you in?
Get out of here.
I did.
Morning.
Weren't you supposed to come later.
What the hell?
Get rid of her.
Now.
Meg,
there is no time.
Finish putting it on, out there.
What are you doing?
Brooks.
Listen, I'll call you
and explain everything.
What? No.
Just...
Just... just go, please.
Brooks.
Brooks, stop it.
Don't go outside.
Damn it.
Forget about the damn dog.
Wake up.
Our family's future is being
decided right now.
In debt or in wealth.
Got it, son?
Got it.
Then get your shit together.
Hurry up.
Walt,
What are you
standing around for?
We have a few hours
to find you a decent girl.
Do you really want
your father’s millions to go
to someone
who doesn't deserve it?
I'm in.
You'll get a decent girl.